RG 169:007, Connecticut Forest and Park Association
Connecticut State Library
- Series 15. Maps, 1929-1978
  - Sleeping Giant on Mount Carmel, circa 1930; Giant sized map showing Hamden and Wallingford, Connecticut; also includes Sleeping Giant Park Association, Inc. Annual meeting notice. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Tunxis Trail, 1970-1978; Barkhamsted, New Hartford, and Nepaug. (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Series 16. Artifacts, 1996, undated
  - Slide viewer and 35mm film, undated; Pana-Vue 2 by View-Master slide viewer, one uncut strip black and white film possibly of Tree Farm, Water Fall, abandon building and one Koday Advantix film cassette-possibly empty. (Box 46, Folder Item 1)
  - Badges, undated; Three Connecticut's Blue-Blazed Hiking Trails: Mattabesett Trail and Quinnipiac Trail; and two Connecticut Forest and Park Association (CFPA) Trails Volunteer.; 5 badges (Box 46, Folder Item 2)
  - Silver and Blue ribbon, 1996; Inscription on back: Hartford Flower Show, Nancy MaCall, Melissa Jones, Mary Lyons. (Box 46, Folder Item 3)
  - Picture signs and word signs, undated; Possibly used for display, mounted on foam core are six titled painted pictures - buildings shopping areas, streets, parking lots, parks, playgrounds; eight word signs - increase land value, provide shade, create oxygen, beautify sites, reduce noise, enrich soil, curtail erosion, and harbor wildlife. (Box 46, Folder Item 4)
  - Picture signs and word signs, undated; Wildlife. (Box 46, Folder Item 4)
  - Trail signs, undated; Metal signs for Connecticut Forest and Park Association (CFPA) private conservation land and CFPA blue-blazed hiking trails; This trail is on private land and used only by the courtesy of the owner, whose rights must be respected, printed on material; Woods closed by proclamation of the governor; Connecticut Forestry Association, 1895; Connecticut Forest and Park Association (arrow) meeting.; Metal: 2 white and 5 blue; 9 cloth; 6 CFPA meeting; 1 woods closed; 1 Connecticut Forest. (Box 46, Folder Folder 2)
  - The Sleeping Giant Park Association, Inc., undated; Organized 1924. (Box 46, Folder Folder 3)
- Series 17. Removable Media, 1994-2005
  RESTRICTED
  - Articles for Spring/Summer Connecticut Woodlands, 2001; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 1)
    This item is separated from these records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - C.C.C. article by Jeanne Filek, 1st draft, 2000 November 22; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 2)
  - CFPA Annual Report 2000, 1998-2001; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 3)
  - CFPA Headquarters / CFPA Logo, 1998-2000; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 4)
  - CFPA rainfall presentation, 2002 October; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Woodlands winter, 2000-2001; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 6)
  - Detailed Environmental Annual Report, 1994; 2 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 7)
    1 floppy disk contains the PDF report and 1 contains the Adobe software.
  - Landowner seminar, 1999 September-2000 March; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 8)
    Floppy disk contains ten Microsoft Word documents.
  - Metacomet Trail (J. Barnett), 2000 June 29; 1 - 3.5 in. floppy disk (Folder 9)
    Floppy disk contains a Microsoft Word document.
  - CFPA, 2005; 1 compact disc, 34.6 MB (Folder 1)
    20 jpegs.
    This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - CFPA volunteers building a bridge, 2005; 1 compact disc, 86.6 MB (Folder 2)
    10 tif.
  - CFPA volunteers picnic, Day Pond, 2004 September 19; 1 compact disc, 22.4 MB (Folder 3)
    26 jpegs, 30 dat, 6 vcd, 1 app, 1 cfg, 1 fnt, and 1 rtf.
    From Bob Schoff.
  - Connecticut Woodlands spring photos, 2001; 1 compact disc, 6.46 MB (Folder 4)
    8 jpegs and 1 tif.
  - Bridgeport and Hartford Olmsted Legacy Trail photo and descrips, 2004; 1 compact disc, 147 MB (Folder 5)
    B. Yaeger, copy 2.
    176 jpegs, 2 Microsoft Word documents.
  - Manchester, Meriden, New Britain, New London, and West Hartford Olmsted Legacy Trail photo and descrips, 2004; 1 compact disc, 195 MB (Folder 6)
    200 jpegs and 1 Microsoft Word document.
  - Middletown, Cromwell, New Haven, and Waterbury Olmsted Legacy Trail, 2004; 1 compact disc, 299 MB (Folder 7)
    257 jpegs, 3 Microsoft Word documents, 1 gif, and 1 psd.
  - Olmsted, 2005; 1 compact disc, 7 MB (Folder 8)
    8 jpegs.
  - Trails workshop, 2005 May; 1 compact disc, 9.72 MB (Folder 9)
    11 jpegs.
  - Visual Identity for Reproduction, 2003; 1 compact disc, 702 KB (Folder 10)
    4 eps.
- Series 18. Sound Recordings, 1966-1993
  - Annual Trails, 1993 June 12; Recorded on both sides.; 1 sound cassette (Box 47)
  - CFPA Annual Meeting, 1989 June 19; Recorded on both sides.; 1 sound cassette (Box 47)
  - CFPA Annual, 1990 June 11-16; Side 2: Public Radio - Forests.; 1 sound cassette (Box 47)
  - Forest are more than trees; An educational slide/tape presentation of the National Wildlife Federation, 1989 June 19; Boxed set also contains slides and educator's guide book.; 1 sound cassette + supplemental material (Box 47)
  - Governor Conference on Natural Beauty, 1966 March 10; Tape #1 - Panel #1, speeches by Seed & Glison, panel questions & replies; Tape #2 - Panel #2, speeches by Wallace; Tape #3 - Panel #2, speeches by Mills & Spreiregen; Tape 4 - Panel #2, (continued) Spreiregen; Tape #5 - Panel #3, speeches by Williams, Foster.; Reel 4 & 5 recorded on both sides.; 5 reels - 5 in. sound tape reel (Box 47)
  - "Hiking Connecticuts Blue Blazed Trails", 1987 September 30; Also contains a script and slides, see slide series for both.; 1 sound cassette + supplemental material (Box 47)
  - Keeping Connecticut green, 1984 April 19; Also contains slides, see slide series - container 3.; 1 sound cassette + supplemental material (Box 47)
  - "Keeping Connecticut green" Connecticut Forest & Parks Association, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 47)
  - Lufkin, 1974 April 22; 1 reel - 5 in. sound tape reel (Box 47)
  - Public radio, 1990 April 11; 1 sound cassette (Box 47)
  - Ramble tape, undated; 1 reel - 5 in. sound tape reel (Box 47)
  - The Woodlands demo - Guy W. Dedell, undated; All the music is produced and performed by Guy W. Dedell.; 1 sound cassette (Box 47)
- Series 19. Film and Video, 1998, undated
  - CFPA - Jerry Rankin, 1998 March 4; 1 videocassette (VHS), 1/2 in. (Box 47)
  - CFPA Annual Meeting, 1998 June 15; 2 videocassette (VHS), 1/2 in. (Box 47)
  - Seasons Of The Forest, Connecticut Forest & Park Association, undated; 1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. (Box 47)
  - Untitled, undated; 1 videocassette (VHS), 1/2 in. (Box 47)